### Contact

william.yahsing.li@gmail.co

www.linkedin.com/in/yaxingwilliam-li (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Amazon Web Services (AWS) Google Cloud Platform (GCP) Flask

#### **Publications**

Highly efficient hydrogen generation from hydrazine borane via a MoOx-promoted NiPd nanocatalyst

# Yaxing Li

Computer Science Master's Candidate at USC | Machine Learning Researcher | Software Engineer

Los Angeles, California, United States

## Summary

Emerging computer scientist with a strong foundation in machine learning and software engineering, currently pursuing a Master's in Computer Science at USC. Within a span of 2 years, I've been at the forefront of groundbreaking projects like the ITHP-DeBERTa model, demonstrating my capability to innovate and excel rapidly in diverse research and technological settings. My unique blend of expertise from Materials Science and Japanese studies provides a holistic and globally informed perspective on problem-solving. As an active researcher and collaborator with prestigious institutions, I'm eager to continue making significant contributions to the world of technology.

### Experience

A5 Labs
Software Engineer Intern
September 2023 - Present (2 months)
Foster City, California, United States

USC Viterbi School of Engineering 7 months

Course Producer for CSCI 455 August 2023 - Present (3 months) Los Angeles, California, United States

Student Researcher of Cyber Physical Systems Group April 2023 - Present (7 months)

Los Angeles, California, United States

JITRI Institute for Process Modeling and Optimization Technology Solutions Intern September 2021 - June 2022 (10 months) Suzhou, Jiangsu, China

## Education

University of Southern California Master of Science - MS, Computer Science